A Guide to the Papers of Robert Frost, 1873-1981
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I. Manuscripts
  - Subseries B. Manuscripts by Frost children
    - Notebook entitled "Many Storys" by Irma Frost, given to her parents for Christmas. Includes "Travelling," "Climbing Mount," "My Rabbit Story," "Vines," and "English Dogs." On the front cover is a drawing of a small dog, 1912 [December 25]; AMsS, 48 p. (Box 2)
    - Notebook with red cardboard covers containing poetry and short stories by Lesley Frost. Includes "Spring," "June," "The Valley of Mist," "The Cloud," "Fear," "An Ancient Story," and "Reflection", 1912-1913; AMsS, 96 p. (Box 2)
    - Black leatherette notebook entitled "On the Road to Fleuraclea" by Lesley Frost, dedicated to "Papa" [ Robert Frost], and containing poetry and short stories, 1913 November-December; AMsS, 100 p. (Box 2)
    - Black leatherette notebook entitled "An Important Year by Four Children," dedicated to "Papa and Mamma," written while residing in "The Bungalow," Beaconsfield, England. Contains diagrams, short stories, poetry, and illustrations, 1913; AMs, 125 p. (Box 2)
    - "The Bouquet," a magazine created, edited and distributed by the Frost children while in England. Contains poetry, stories, and drawings. The contributors to this issues are Amy Smith, Carol, Irma, Lesley and Marjorie Frost, and Merfyn Thomas, 1914 June; TMs, 33 p. (Box 3)
    - "The Bouquet." Includes contributions by Lesley, Carol, Marjorie, and Irma Frost; Amy Smith; Bronwen and Merfyn Thomas; and, a signed poem, "Pea-sticks," by Robert Frost, 1914 July; TMs, 60 p. (Box 3)
    - "The Bouquet." Contains poems, stories, and illustrations by Lesley, Marjorie, and Irma Frost, and a poem, "Locked Out," by Robert Frost, 1914 September; TMs, 31 p. (Box 3)
    - Notebook with black covers containing drafts of poems and stories, including "Reflection," "After the Cows," "A Good House-Cleaning Anyway," and "What a Swallow Is," which was used in the July 1914 issue of "The Bouquet", AMs, 72 p. (Box 3)
    - "The Rein A Magazine 6. War Number," a children's magazine put out by Delphis Gardner, a friend of Lesley Frost, with contributions by Charles Lawndes, Delphis Gardner, Denys Stephens, Joan Jasper, Venyan Stephens, and a Belgian boy, [ca. 1915 January]; AMsS, 35 p. (Box 3)
    - "The Bouquet." Contains poetry, stories, riddles, and drawings by Lesley, Irma, Carol, and Marjorie Frost, Merfyn Thomas, and a poem, "The Combe," by Edward Thomas, [1915] April; TMs, 28 p. (Box 3)
    - "The Bouquet." Contains poetry, stories, and drawings by Lesley, Irma, and Carol Frost, Beulah Huckins, Amy Smith, and Merfyn Thomas, 1915 June; TMs, 35 p. (Box 3)
    - "The Bouquet," bearing "Franconia, N. H. U.S.A." as its place of creation. Contains drawings, stories, and poetry by Irma, Carol, and Marjorie Frost, and a poem, "Nettles," by Edward Thomas, 1916 June; TMs, 21 p. (Box 3)
    - Four notebooks containing stories and verse written by Carol Frost[microfilm only], 1912-1913; TMs (Box 3)
  - Manuscripts by others about Robert Frost
    - Notes made by John T. Bartlettafter various conversations with Robert Frost, 1932-1937; T & AMs, 62 p. (Box 3)
    - First chapter of a book on Robert Frost by Margaret Bartlett [in notebook], n.d.; AMs, 8 p. (Box 3)
    - "Mr. Pope Communicates his Sentiments to the Writers' Conference", n.d.; Mimeograph, 2 p. (Box 3)
    - "Robert Frost I" by Elizabeth Jennings. Draft in pencil in blue notebook, n.d.; AMs, 94 p. (Box 4)
    - "Robert Frost II" by Elizabeth Jennings. Draft in pencil in blue notebook, n.d.; AMs, 93 p. (Box 4)
    - Poem, "Death Song of the Last American Indian," of unknown author, sent by Robert Newdick to Robert Frost with Frost's autograph reply on the sheets [original item filed in "Letters" series], TMs (copy), 2 p. (Box 4)
    - History of the "Robert Frost House," [originally in Ann Arbor] Greenfield Village, Michigan by Bernice S. Lurie, with a picture of the house from Antiques, October 1964, 1973; AMs, 5 p. (Box 4)
    - "The Uncertain Harvest," an account of the author's visit to Derry Farm, by Dorothy Judd Hall, ca. 1962 December; TMs (mimeo), 6 p. (Box 4)
    - "Robert Frost As A Public Personality" by Gloria M. McCall, Master of Arts thesis, Texas Christian University, inscribed to Mrs. Lesley Limic. Bound, 1964 August; TMs (carbon), ca. 103 p. (Box 4)
    - "Robert Frost of Brewster Village" by Erastus H. Hewitt, read to the Cambridge Historical Society, 1965 May 25; TMs (copy), 15 p. (Box 4)
    - "Robert Frost: An Afterimage" by Dorothy Judd Hall, inscribed to Lesley Frost Ballantine, 1975 February 4; TMs (copy), 17 p. (Box 4)
    - "Realms of the Spirit: An Inquiry Into Robert Frost's Sense of Place," by Ronald Bieganowski, doctoral dissertation, Fordham University, 1977; TMs, 200 p. (Box 4)
    - A Swinger of Birches A Portrait of Robert Frost by Sidney Cox, published by New York University Press, 1957; Page Proof (Box 4)
    - Meeting of Mounted Men by Ray Nash, n.d.; Page Proof (Box 4)
      Describes the collaboration of between Frost and J. J. Lankes; inscribed by Frost to Earl Bernheimer. 6261-bi
    - Text of CBS radio program Invitation to Learning, 1946 August 18; TMs, 13 p. (Box 4)
      Featuring John Hall Wheelock, Donald Stauffer and Theodore Spencer discussing Frost's poetry; inscribed by Frost to Russel Alberts. 6261-bi
- Series II. Letters
  - Subseries A. Correspondence of Robert Frost, Elinor Frost and the Frost Family
    - Subseries 1. Parents of Robert Frost
      - William Prescott Frost, Jr.to Isabelle "Belle" Moodie, ca. 1873 February; ALS, 7 p. (Box 5)
        A heart-felt letter, declaring his feelings for her and proposing marriage.
      - [William Prescott Frost, Jr.], San Francisco, California, to "My Darling Wife" [Isabell Moodie Frost], 1873 July 13; AL, 8 p. (Box 5)
        Urging her to join him out west, telling of his success in selling articles to newspapers, and giving information on train travel. [incomplete].
      - [ William Prescott Frost, Jr.] to "My Dear Grandmother" [ Mary Blunt Frost], 1874 October 25; ALS, 3 p. (Box 5)
        Discussing the changes in his life, including moving out west, becoming a city editor, and getting married and having a child [Robert Frost].
      - William P. Frost, Jr.to "Dear Grandmother" [ Mary Blunt Frost], 1874 November 29; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Acknowledging her letter and discussing extended family.
      - Isabelle "Belle" (Moodie) Frost to "My Darling Husband" [William Prescott Frost, Jr.], [1876] November 1; ALS, 7 p. (Box 5)
        Following her return east and the birth of their daughter [ Jeanie Florence Frost], writing that "Bob is just as queer as ever about some things..."
    - Subseries 2. Robert Frost, Elinor Frost and the Frost Family
      - Kathleen Morrison, Cambridge, Massachusetts, on "Homer Noble Farm/Ripton/Vermont" letterhead, to Clifton Waller Barrett, 1951 April 10; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Concerning Robert Frost's manuscript in progress and a reserve fund in Vermontthat she has set aside on Frost's behalf.
      - Two paper wrappers inscribed by Robert Frost to Clifton Waller Barrett, [1952], n.d.; ANS (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to [Lascelles] Abercrombie, 1915 September 21; ALS, 7 p. (Box 5)
        Commenting on the Abercrombrie's troubles, Elinor Frost's poor health "just at this moment when our fortunes begin to look up a little --," and discussing the effects and current status of the disastrous contract with his first publisher, Mrs. Nutt. Postscript of September 30 written after receiving legal advice concerning his contract with Mrs. Nutt; discussing his obligations and intentions in fulfilling the contract.
      - Robert Frost to [Lascelles] Abercrombie, n.d.; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
        Commenting on his sending "something more than books: this is friendship."
      - Robert Frost to Earle Bernheimer, 1936 March 2; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
        Indicating his willingness to autograph anything for him and giving his various places of residences.
      - Elinor Frost, Amherst, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, [1937] April 19; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Concerning Robert Frost's slow recovery from nervous exhaustion, and his willingness to autograph some books for him.
      - Robert Frost, Boston, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, 1938 November 8; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Acknowledging his fine collection of Frost's books and writing his willingness [to inscribe them].
      - Robert Frost, Boston, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, Kansas City, Missouri, 1939 November 18; ALS, 2 p. w/env. (Box 5)
        Writing that he "might not be able to refuse serious money for the unique Twilight, " with notation at top, "Beginning of negotiations--November. 1939. E. J. B."
      - Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, Los Angeles, California, 1941 June 1; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Writing that he is in need of two thousand dollars and offering the sale of two of his most valuable manuscripts, with note on verso in red pencil, "1 year after purchase of Twilight. O. K."
      - Edward W. Forbes, Saturday Club, to Robert Frost, 1943 April 20; TLS, 1 p. (Box 5)
        Extending membership to Frost, inscribed "For Earle to keep for me R. F."
      - Kathleen Morrison, Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, with enclosed printed letter, April 20, 1943 [see above], 1943 April 27; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost, Ripton, Vermont, to Earle Bernheimer, 1943 July 15; ALS, 3 p. (Box 5)
        Mentioning "that Jonathan Cape had brought out A Witness Tree in a pretty little war economy format in England, " his being touched by the interest, and his appreciation of and obligation to the English. Stating that his contact with the war is through his grandson, William Prescott Frost III, who enlisted. Discussing his transition as faculty from Harvard to Dartmouth.
      - Robert Frost, [Florida], to Earle Bernheimer, [1944 March 7]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 5)
        Listing his spring schedule, discussing personal health and other news; and, the war and that "our kind of people are beginning to speak up for our kind of world," mentioning Louis Bromfield, John Chamberlain, and Ray Nash.
      - Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, 1944 March 21; Telegram (Box 5)
        ... "good joke between friends."
      - Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, 1944 March 22; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Reassuring him that the accident could not make any difference in their friendship, and promising that he will have the copy of Masque of Reason soon.
      - Robert Frost, Ripton, Vermont, on "Dartmouth College, Hanover, New Hampshire," letterhead, to Earle Bernheimer, 1944 June 10; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
        Discussing his college lectures and still promising to send the copy of Masque of Reason.
      - Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, 1944 Spring; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Indicating that Dartmouthis anxious to obtain Bernheimer's collection, and praising Ray Nashof Dartmouthas a great authority and as being instrumental in Frost being made the George Ticknor Fellow in the Humanities.
      - Kathleen Morrison, Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, 1944 December 5; TLS, 1 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Enclosing the copy of Robert Frost's "A Masque of Reason" and promising to send a poem, "Two Leading Lights," to use for his Christmas card.
      - Kathleen Morrison, Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, Beverly Hills, California, 1944 December 6; Telegram (Box 5)
        Saying that Robert Frost suggests he use the poem sent the previous day for a Christmas card.
      - Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Earle Bernheimer, 1944 December 14; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
        Enclosing [poem] identified at top as "The original jottings that finally became the poem, 'Provide, Provide.' E. J. B." Writing that the proofs of New Hampshire and Mountain Interval have turned up.
      - Robert Frost, Ripton, Vermont, to Earle Bernheimer, 1945 August 8; ALS, 4 p. (Box 5)
        Writing that he has had the idea for the final touch needed for Masque of Mercy, and that he will send it to him soon. Mentioning a party given in Frost's honor by Henry Holt and Company, a possible lecture at Berkeley, and his interest in writing on the second Masque or a poem now and then.
      - Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, on "Dartmouth College, Hanover, New Hampshire" letterhead, to Earle Bernheimer, 1947 January 14; ALS, 3 p. (Box 5)
        Mentioning personal news including the divorce of his daughter, explaining that the name Twilight came from an expression used in real estate, and discussing his works Masque and Steeplebush.
      - Robert Frost, South Miami, Florida, on "Dartmouth College, Hanover, New Hampshire" letterhead, to Earle Bernheimer, 1947 February 20; TLS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Concerning a social event at the Bohemian Cluband a lecture at a nearby college, with autograph note at end, "leaving here for Cambridge this week..."
      - Robert Frost to Earle Bernheimer, [1947 July 3]; AL, 2 p. (Box 5)
        (Incomplete), writing news of Steeplebush and the second Masque, and of his many spring lecture engagements.
      - Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, on "Dartmouth College, Hanover, New Hampshire" letterhead, to Earle Bernheimer, 1947 October 16; TLS, 3 p. (Box 5)
        Acknowledging his generosity and understanding of Frost manuscripts and books; giving permission to use "The Waterfall" for a Christmas card; and commenting on his daughter's divorce and commitment to a hospital for the insane and on Bernheimer's Frost collection.
      - Robert Frost, Ripton, Vermont, to Earle Bernheimer, Beverly Hills, California, 1948 September 10; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Mentioning his troubles in regard to his daughter's divorce and insanity; and, compromising on his use of a passage from The Guardeen.
      - Wrapper addressed to Earle Bernheimer from Robert Frost, n.d.; ANS (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost, South Shaftsbury, Vermont, to Mr. Bird, 1933 June 7; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Concerning a lecture tour in Californiaand asking for particulars.
      - L[e] B[aron] Russell] Briggs, Dean, Harvard College, Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Robert Frost, 1899 March 31; TLS, 1 p. (Box 5)
        Testifying to Frost's honorable dismissal from college.
      - Robert Frost, Franconia, New Hampshire, to "My dear Mr. Brown", 1915 October 27; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Regretfully unable to think of something clever to write in his books and having "to end ignominously by copying you out a poem or two that I care a little for."
      - Robert Frost to [Abbie Farwell] Brown, [1916 May 26]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Thanking her for the book and the dedication and assuring her that the book will be for all six of them; and, calling it "a brown day" as he also received mail from Alice Brownand George Browne.
      - Robert Frost, Metheun, Massachusetts, to [Alice] Brown, 1915 January 15; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
        Concerning an arrangement for several authors to read to her, and mentioning Amy Lowell.
      - Robert Frost, Amherst, Massachusetts, to [Alice] Brown, 1918 November 2; ALS, 3 p. (Box 5)
        Concerning some books he has to inscribe for her, and saying that he will use "some irrelevant poem" of his as an inscription; and, reminiscing about his visit to Boston.
      - Elinor Frost, Beaconsfield, Bucks, England, to Mrs. Harry Brown, Colebrook, New Hampshire, 1912 October 25; ALS, 6 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Describing London, their cottage and the town of Beaconsfield, and the people of England.
      - Robert Frost, Amherst, Massachusetts, to Cyril Clemens, Webster Groves, Missouri, 1937 April 13; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Accepting the honor of having a book dedicated to him.
      - Frank D. Fackenthal, Columbia University, New York, to Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1943 May 3; Telegram (Box 5)
        Congratulating him on the Pulitzer Poetry Prize for A Witness Tree, with Frost's autograph reply beneath, "Getting it for the fourth time rather stops me from saying anything against a fourth term as president. R. F."
      - Robert Frost, Amherst, Massachusetts, to Mr. Hazlett, The American Mercury, 1933 December 15; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
        Asking if he is still interested in some of his poems, with a copy of "Lost in Heaven."
      - Robert Frost, South Shaftsbury, Vermont, to Robert Silliman Hillyer, [Pomfret, Connecticut], [1924 January 25]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Thanking him for wanting "The Census-Taker" and enclosing the three-page TMsS poem; and, commenting that Hillyer's poems are "in the right road for you. Now go the whole length of it."
      - Robert Frost, Amherst, Massachusetts, to Robert Silliman Hillyer, [Boston, Massachusetts], [1924 March 12]; ALS, 2 p. w.env (Box 5)
        Writing that he has a volume of poetry in safekeeping for him and asking whether he wants him to read in public for him.
      - Robert Frost, South Shaftsbury, Vermont, to Robert Silliman Hillyer, Pomfret, Connecticut, 1924 July 24; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Concerning plans for November.
      - Robert Frost, Amherst, Massachusetts, to Robert Silliman Hillyer, Cambridge, Massachusetts, [1931 February 4]; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Concerning his publisher's refusal to send a copy of Frost's latest book to Hillyer for review.
      - Robert Frost, Franconia, New Hampshire, to Robert Silliman Hillyer, Pomfret, Connecticut, 1934 September 5; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Offering to nominate him for membership in "the Institute" and praising him for receiving the "reward from the Pulitzers."
      - Robert Frost, Key West, Florida, to Robert Silliman Hillyer, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1935 March 22; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Accepting an invitation to visit his alma mater Harvard Collegeon April 17th.
      - Robert Frost, San Antonio, Texas, to Robert Silliman Hillyer, [Boston, Massachusetts], 1937 February 9; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 5)
        Concerning Frost's inability to write a poem for his reading [at Harvard College] the previous September and Hillyer's support; and, a request from Shirley Barkerfor assistance in obtaining a scholarship at Radcliffe.
      - Robert Frost, South Shaftsbury, Vermont, to Robert Silliman Hillyer, 1937 June 16; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
        Sending congratulations on his latest honor.
      - Robert Frost, Concord Corners, Vermont, to Robert Silliman Hillyer, Pomfret, Connecticut, 1937 September 15; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Robert Silliman Hillyer, 1938 July 20; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Robert Silliman Hillyer, 1938 August 12; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 5)
      - H[enry] H[olt]to Robert Frost, 1947 February 5; TL (carbon), 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to [Henry] Holt, 1947 February 20; TLS, 1 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John S. Van E. Kohn, 1938 September 2; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Miss Lamb, 1926 July 10; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Miss Lamb, 1926 August 6; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Mansfield, 1920 January 20; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to [Harold] Monro, 1913 November 25; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Thomas B. Mosher, with AMsS poem, "Reluctance," on verso, 1912 February 19; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to [Thomas B.] Mosher, 1912 March 4; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to [Thomas B.] Mosher, 1914 January 20; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to [Thomas B.] Mosher, 1914 July 27; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to [Thomas B.] Mosher, 1914 October; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to [Thomas B.] Mosher, 1915 March 22; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - David Nutt to L. M. Isaacs re A Boy's Will, 1927 May 14; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Charles H. Oliphant to [ ], recommendation of Robert Frost as a teacher, 1897 September 17; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Robert Partridge, 1937 January 21; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Robert Partridge, 1937 April 20; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to "My dear Mrs. Penniman", 1920 March 17; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Lola Ridge, 1919 April 24; ALS, 3 p. (Box 5)
      - Wilbur E. Rowell to Robert Frost, 1912 July 10; TLS, 1 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Elizabeth M. Tarney, 1927 January 25; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to Elizabeth M. Tarney, n.d.; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to [W. Orton] Tewson, 1925 August 25; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
      - Louis Henry Cohn to R. V. Thornton, 1949 April 5; TLS, 1 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to R. V. Thornton, 1954 May 9; ALS, 1 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to R. V. Thornton, 1954 November 11; ALS, 1 p w/env (Box 5)
      - Jack W. Hagstrom to R. V. Thornton, 1955 September 8; TLS, 1 p w/env (Box 5)
      - Kathleen Morrison to R. V. Thornton, 1955 October 15; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to [John Hall] Wheelock, 1932 December 15; ALS, 2 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1912 December 25; ALS, 3 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1913 February 26; ALS, 3 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1913 mid March]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 5)
      - Elinor Frost to Margaret Bartlett, 1913 March 18; ALS, 4 p. (Box 5)
      - Irma Frost to Margaret Bartlett, [1913 March 18]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1913 April 4]; ALS, 5 p. w/env (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1913 June 12]; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 5)
      - Elinor Frost to Margaret Bartlett, 1913 July 3; ALS, 9 p. w/env (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1913 July 4; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1913] August 6; ALS, 4 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1913 August 7]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1913 August 30; ALS, 8 p. (Box 5)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1913 October 9]; ALS, 6 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1913 November 18]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1913] December 8; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1914 February 22; ALS, 10 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1915] April 20; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1915 May 8]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1915 May 20; AL (fragment), 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1915 June 8; ALS, 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1915 June 17; ALS, 3 p. (Box 6)
        Enclosing a newspaper clipping from the New York Evening Post, June 11, 1915.
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1915 July 2]; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Elinor Frost to Margaret Bartlett, [1915 July 2]; ALS, 8 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1915 August 8; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1915 August 24; ALS, 1 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1915 September 9; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1915 October 21; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1915 December 2; ALS, 1 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1916 January]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1916 May; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1916 September 28; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1917 February 13; ALS, 3 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1917] April 25; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1917 August 13]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 6)